CURRICULUM VITAE



Rufaida Jumaa

Address: Frødalen 24 1sal tv, 3400 Hillerød

Born 01/01/1993



+45 20710141



E-mail



GitHub



LinkedIn



Online portfolio

SKILLS

Sitecore Umbraco

HTML/CSS
JavaScript(ES6)
NodeJS
MySQL
React
Git

LANGUAGES

Arabic (Mother tongue)

Danish (Fluent for daily use level)

English (Professional level)

French (Basic understanding)

PROFILE

I am an ambitious and curious person with a great passion for Web Development. Since I moved to Denmark, back in 2017, I have learned 2 languages, English and Danish, studied Web Development intensively and joined Kruso as a web developer. I have had a break in my career because I became a mother for the second time. I am now ready to embrace a career as a Web Developer where I can use my WebDevelopment skills from the HackYourFuture Full Stack course together with my background in Information Technology Engineering.

WORK EXPERIENCE

09/2018 – 11/2018 KRUSO A/S - Copenhagen/ Denmark Frontend Developer working mainly with Umbraco, Sitecore, HTML, CSS, JavaScript.

02/2018 – 08/2018 KRUSO A/S - Copenhagen/ Denmark Web Developer internship working with backend & frontend development tasks within different departments of the company.

EDUCATION

05/2017 – 14/1/2018 - HackYourFuture - Copenhagen/ Denmark Full Stack Web Development bootcamp, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node.js, MySQL, Express, React, GIT.

09/2011 – 11/2016 - DAMASCUS UNIVERSITY - Damascus/ Syria Bachelor of Information Technology Engineering - Computer Systems and Networks

5 year education, Received Bachelor of Science, GPA (73.64) (Equivalent to the Danish "professions-bachelor som diplomingeniør - IT")

2010 – 08/2011 - SYRIAN MINISTRY OF EDUCATION - Damascus/ Syria General Certificate Of Secondary Education (Scientific Section) Focus on Mathematics, Physics, Chemistry and Natural Sciences, Arabic, English and French, GPA (95.83).

VOLUNTEER WORK

I have joined HackYourFuture community again to give back, I support the open office, mentoring in git classes, helping with feedback for application process and interviewing applicants.